

## SHAURYA SINGH

A talented, driven and flexible graphic designer with a proven record of delivering creative and innovative design solutions. Now looking for a suitable graphic designer position with an ambitious and high profile company.

## O CONTACT

- **(2)** +91 9599633375
- shaurya806@gmail.com
- Sector 17 A, Gurgaon

## X SOFTWARE SKILLS









Other Software: MS Word, PowrPoint, Excel, InDesign, Adobe XD

## HOBBIES







Movies

Photography

## PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Birth: 27th Dec 1995 Nationality: Indian

Religion: Hindu

Marital status: Unmarried

#### WHY SHOULD YOU HIRE ME?

With 4 years of experience working as a qualified graphic and web designer, I have worked with a variety of companies locally and internationally, designing and producing quality print and digital design solutions. Offering unique solutions for each client is a major strength, with effective visual design driving brand recognition and customer response.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Graphic & UI Designer | Nov 2019 - Feb 2020 ~ Currently Freelancing APICON 2020, AGRA

Job profile: Designer on contract basis

My role includes day-to-day management of website updates, communicating with printers, social media promotion, and design all required creative for the conference.

### Graphic & Website Designer | Jan 2017 - Oct 2019

#### Cox and Kings Ltd. Gurgaon

Job profile: Graphic & Website Designer

Developing concepts and artwork for the conference department, creating graphic design solutions from concept through to completion. Responsible for developing and creating both digital and print design for a wide range of print and online campaigns, publications & advertising.

#### **Duties:**

- » Managing, producing and designing projects from brief to
- » Designing & creating marketing & e-marketing materials on a range of projects
- » Presenting finalized ideas & concepts to clients, colleagues & senior managers
- » Involved in designing advertisements, brochures, handouts, flyers and event management.
- » Working with a range of media, including photography, to create the final artwork
- » Coordinate with registered vendor for various projects

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Graphic Designer | Jan 2014 - Dec 2016

#### Freelancing for Retail 360, Gurgaon

Job profile: Graphic Designer (Internship + Designer)

My role includes the management of printing artworks, design all required project artworks for Microsoft Lumia.

#### **SOME HIGHLIGHTED PROJECTS**

#### Pedicon 2018 at Nagpur, Maharashtra

55th National Conference of Indian Academy of Pediatrics



#### Petrotech - 2019

The 13<sup>th</sup> International Oil and Gas Conference & Exhibition "Petrotech – 2019" a global event hosted by the Ministry of Petroleum and Natural Gas, Government of India, in and related sectors including alternative energy, engineering and technology.



#### Microsoft Lumia

Artworking for Microsoft Lumia phone (BnB, 535, Asha)





#### **EDUCATIONS**

High School - UP Board | 2010

Institute: LPK Inter College

Intermediate (PCM) - UP Board | 2012

Institute: LPK Inter College

Diploma in Graphic & Web Design | 2013-2014

Institute: Arena Animation (Aptech), Gurgaon

Bachelor of Computer Application | 2016

Institute: Sri Satya Sai University of Technology & Medical Sciences

# → LANGUAGES 🙉

Englis	h		
Speak			
Read			
Write			

Hindi	
Speak	
Read	
Write	